Okay. So, uh, in order to sign into your
GitHub desktop, you do have to have a
GitHub account. In order to create one
of those, you'll go to github.com. You
should land on a page that looks
something like this. It varies based on
the time, but as long as you're on
github.com, you're in the right spot.
Okay. There are two ways to do this. Um,
you can click the sign up button at the
top, or you can enter an email here. So,
I'm going to say test@gmail.com
and click sign up. And that will let you
enter in your username, your email, your
password, your username, um, and where
you are. And then you can go ahead and
click create account. Once you've done
that, you should be able to sign into
your GitHub desktop. So, I'm going to
change tabs to my GitHub desktop.
And I'm going to say sign in to
github.com. And it's going to open up
here. And I'm going to type in uh my
username. And then I'm going to type in
my password. And that's actually in
password manager. So, I'm going to pause
this video until I have that password.
Okay. Once you've finally logged in,
you'll want to um click continue to
authorize this user to access GitHub
Desktop. I'll hit continue. It'll say,
can it access all of this information?
I'm going to say yes. And then it says,
do you want to allow it to open your
app? I'm going to hit allow. And um I
want it to use my GitHub account name
and email address. I'm going to leave
that as my name. And I'm going to go
ahead and click finish. Um then it's if
you are on a Mac, it is going to ask if
you want to move your desktop to the
applications folder. Um you can move and
restart. I'm going to hit not now. But
if you see this page, you have
successfully logged into GitHub desktop.
Great work. and we'll pick up in the
next